Help me. please. I need help.
I don't know where my parents are!
Some people broke into our house
and stole all this money.
I could hear
my parents yelling downstairs.
Please send help!
Dad?
I'm just calling 911! I'm calling 911!
I'm okay! I'm all right!
You know what? Just stay there. Okay?
Jennifer?
You okay?
You know what? You can't worry about this.
I mean. we learn.
But you did what you had to do. right?
That's the bottom line.
I think I heard my mom say
or moan something.
and then they did one more pop
before they left.
And then one of the guys said.
"We have to go now. It's been too long."
And then they ran out the door...
Help me. please. I need help.
They had guns. and they were
holding my parents at gunpoint.
I can't. I'm tied. My hands are tied.
I couldn't understand why Bich was killed.
I was very emotional.
I could not believe this had happened.
It was so bad.
There were times
that I came to her house to hang out
to eat dinner with them.
They were very hospitable.
Very generous people...
who loved their friends.
Hann works five days a week
and some overtime.
He certainly isn't involved in the Mafia
or gambling or drinking.
He's just a humble. down-to-earth man.
And Jen was getting crank calls too?
Someone invaded your home. ma'am?
Someone broke in.
and I heard shots. like pops.
I don't know what's happening.
I'm tied upstairs.
They just broke in and tied you up?
Yes.
Bich said that her daughter
had studied to be a pharmacist.
but after graduating.
she still couldn't find a job.
She worried and talked a lot about it.
All she wanted was
for her to be successful.
And not to be looked down on by society.
What school did they think
you were going to?
Ryerson.
They would drive me down to Toronto.
and they thought I was going to class.
But I wasn't.
Help me. please. I need help.
Someone broke in.
and I heard shots. like pops.
I don't know what's happening.
I'm tied up...
I'm tied upstairs!
- Can you lock your doors?
- I can't.
I'm tied!
My hands are tied behind my back!
I had my cell phone in my pocket!
It's just me.
You okay still?
Everything's going...
Do you need a bathroom break?
Sorry. I'm just a little rattled.
Okay. You're doing fine.
I'm just trying my best.
The choices I made haven't been the best.
You can't worry about that.
I mean. we learn.
You did what you had to do. right?
It was something
that you felt that you needed to do.
It's just like pieces here
and pieces there and...
I don't...
I don't want to say... something wrong.
Yeah. but all the pieces
are gonna come together.
and it's all gonna fit.
Because what you're saying
is the truth. right?
Let me just clear the hallway.
and then I'll escort you out. Okay?
Help me. please.
Ma'am. calm down. What's going on?
Someone broke in
and I heard shots. like pops.
I don't know what's happening.
I'm tied upstairs.
I want to do it.
When I was four.
- Yeah.
- I get that feeling.
Yes.
When they asked for something.
I'd try to make a document for them.
Student loan...
and report cards.
Using Photoshop.
Not really. no.
Maybe I'd still be with him. I'm not sure.
But he'd already moved on.
He was the person who would just...
filled an empty void for me.
So I felt that a part of me was missing.
I wasn't happy with any parts of my life.
My friends were moving on
with their lives.
and it felt that I wasn't going anywhere.
I was kinda being left behind.
And what was the worst that things got?
I cut myself.
No.
I don't know.
You gave a description
of a Black guy with dreads.
There was no Black guy with
dreads in there.
Okay? He gave a good description
of the guy that you were with.
and he's not even Black.
Why did you say that?
- That's what I remember.
- No.
You're involved in this.
And those guys didn't show up there
to take your money.
They came there to shoot your parents.
I wanted it to stop.
I didn't know who they were.
You're sorry. aren't you?
I can't hear you here.
They were only supposed to take me.
They were supposed to take you?
I needed them to kill me.
Why?
I didn't want to live anymore.
So they were supposed
to take the whole family out?
No. just me.
What went wrong?
I don't know.
Because I didn't wanna be here anymore.
Because I was such a disappointment.
Okay. So how did this play out. then?
It wasn't supposed to happen like this.
What was your request?
Come in.
And take me out.
Two thousand.
Homie. Homeboy.
He texted me.
I told you. $2.000.
and they were supposed to kill me.
And then they called me
to make sure they had access.
A text. "VIP access."
Just to make sure that there was a way in.
Went down. said hello.
Pretended to check the door.
I asked a friend.
Okay. Which one?
One I can't find anymore.
What's his name?
They're placing him under conspiracy.
Wow. You gotta be kidding me.
Fuck. I don't know what's going on. man.
Unreal. Unreal.
Dad?
I'm just calling 911! I'm calling 911!
Yes.
That happened?
I don't think so.
She had planned this before?
She should pay the price.